adside.com 2009-12-09

# DOCLIX: Privacy Policy

DOCLIX respects the privacy of online users. This policy explains the accepted privacy practices for the services available at [www.doclix.com](http://www.doclix.com/) and [www.adside.com](http://www.adside.com/) ("ADSIDE.com") and the use of the _ContextGain_ and _AdSide_ Program Services (collectively, "the Services").

## _AdSide_

_AdSide_ provides online advertisements to affiliate websites that link to the advertisers' websites. DOCLIX does not assume any responsibility or control over any of these websites and content, and this policy does not apply to such websites and content. If you wish to learn how a third party handles your personal information, then you should carefully review its privacy policy.

## _ContextGain_

ContexGain provides end users with access to third party websites and third party content, including Google AdSense generated advertisements. DOCLIX does not assume any responsibility or control over any of these websites and content, and this policy does not apply to such websites and content. If you wish to learn how a third party handles your personal information, then you should carefully review its privacy policy.

## 1\. Personal Information that DOCLIX collects

When you register as an Advertiser or Publisher with the Services, you may be asked to provide personal details, such as your full name, e-mail address, the name of your employer or company, your title, phone number, country of residence, your website's URL, and in the case of _ContextGain_ , your Google AdSense Client ID ("Client ID"). The fields for compulsory completion will be specifically designated.

**The Services are not intended for use by publishers or advertisers under the age of 18. If you are not 18 years of age or older, then you may not register with the Services and must not provide DOCLIX with any of your personal details.**

When you use the Services as a publisher, advertiser or an end user, DOCLIX may collect further information, such as session durations, page impressions, advertisements viewed or clicked on, the Internet protocol (IP) address and the domain name that served you to access the Services, and the geographic location of the computer system that you are using.

DOCLIX may automatically collect information through the use of log files and other means. If you register with any of the Services, then the information gathered will be partially personally identifiable. If you are not a registered user or you are an end user, than we will not knowingly make use of any information which personally identifies you, except as specifically indicated in the policy, or on adside.com.

Further information may be collected when you exchange communications with DOCLIX, for example, when you submit an inquiry to DOCLIX.

## 2\. What does DOCLIX do with your personally identifiable information?

DOCLIX may use personally identifiable information for the following purposes:

  * to provide the Services;
  * to improve and customize your experience with the Services;
  * to provide you with support and handle inquires;
  * to send you updates and notices, to provide you with information pertaining to the Services and to provide you with further marketing and advertising material. At any time you may opt out of the mailing lists, by changing your preferences in your personal account. In any case, DOCLIX will not share your personal identifiable details with any advertisers, without your explicit consent;
  * to facilitate communications with you, and between you and others;
  * to enforce DOCLIX's Terms of Use;
  * to contact you as and when DOCLIX believes it to be necessary;
  * to comply with any applicable law and assist law enforcement agencies as required;
  * to collect fees and debts, and to prevent fraud, misappropriation, infringements, identity thefts and any other misuse of the Services;
  * to pay you, if you are an _AdSide_ publisher;
  * to take any action in any case of dispute, or legal proceeding of any kind between you and DOCLIX, or between you and other users or third parties with respect to, or in relation with the Services;

## 3\. How does DOCLIX use aggregated information?

DOCLIX may use anonymous, statistical or aggregated information about the use of the Services, including any aggregated information related to your personal account, and share, publish, post, disseminate, transmit or otherwise communicate or make available such information, to suppliers, business partners, sponsors, advertisers, affiliates and any other third party, at DOCLIX's sole discretion, provided however, that such information will not identify you personally and that DOCLIX will not knowingly, or intentionally use such information to reveal your identity without your consent, under the terms of this policy.

DOCLIX may also use anonymous, statistical or aggregated information to properly operate the Services, to improve the quality of the Services, to enhance your experience, to create new services, including customized services, to change or cancel existing content or services and for other internal and statistical purposes.

## 4\. How does DOCLIX Share information with others?

DOCLIX does not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties for any of their marketing purposes. DOCLIX may share personally identifiable information with others in any of the following instances, or subject to your explicit consent: 

  * When you use the Services. In this case, DOCLIX will share your information only to the extent required to facilitate your use of the Services; 
  * If DOCLIX believes that you have breached the Terms of Use, or abused your rights to use the Services, or performed any act or omission that DOCLIX believes to be violating any applicable law, rules, or regulations. DOCLIX may share your information in these cases, with law enforcement and other competent authorities and with any third party, as may be required to handle any result of your wrongdoing; 
  * If DOCLIX is required, or believes that it is required by law to share or disclose your information; 
  * In any case of dispute, or legal proceeding of any kind between you and DOCLIX, or between you and other users or third parties with respect to, or in relation with the Services; 
  * In any case where DOCLIX believes that sharing information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or damage to property; 
  * If DOCLIX organizes the operation of the Services within a different framework, or through another legal structure or entity, or if DOCLIX is acquired by, or merged with another entity, provided however, that those entities agree to be bound by the provisions of this policy, with respective changes taken into consideration; 
  * DOCLIX may also share personally identifiable information with companies or organizations connected, or affiliated with it, such as subsidiaries, sister-companies and parent companies.

## 5\. How can you access your personal information? 

If you are a subscriber with any of the Services, then you may access your personal account and edit, or amend your personal information at any time. If you find that the information on your personal account is not accurate, complete or updated, than you must make all necessary changes to correct it. Please keep in mind that false, incorrect, or out dated information may prevent you from registering with the Service, impair DOCLIX's ability to provide you with the Service and the ability to contact you.

## 6\. Data retention

DOCLIX reserves the right at all times to review, retain and disclose any information as it deems necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, as well as DOCLIX's internal needs. However, by doing so DOCLIX does not either expressly or impliedly endorse, affirm or in any manner assume any responsibility for such information.

#### 7\. Information security

DOCLIX implements information security systems and procedures to secure the information stored on its servers. Such systems and procedures reduce the risk of security breaches, but they do not provide absolute security. Therefore, DOCLIX cannot guarantee that the Services are immune to unauthorized access to the information stored therein and to other information security risks.

## 8\. Cookies 

DOCLIX may use cookies when operating the Services. Cookies are packets of information sent by DOCLIX's servers to your web browser and then sent back by the browser. DOCLIX may use cookies for various purposes, such as to save you the need to re-enter your password each time you log-in to one of the Services, to facilitate the use of the Services, to collect information for statistical and analytical purposes, to verify information, to customize the Services to your personal preferences and for information security purposes.

Some of the cookies may expire when the session ends and you exit your browser. Other cookies may be stored on your computer's hard drive. If you wish to block the cookies, then please use the help button in your browser and follow the necessary instructions. However, bear in mind that disabling cookies may complicate or even prevent your use of the Services, or certain features thereof.

## 9\. Advertisements on _ContextGain_

_ContextGain_ Panels display advertisements, alongside related content snippets and links. To use _ContextGain_ as a publisher, you must maintain a valid account with Google AdSense. In the course of setting up your personal account, you will be asked to provide DOCLIX with your Google AdSense Client ID, to facilitate the display of Google AdSense generated advertisements on the _ContextGain_ Panels. DOCLIX shall only use your AdSense Client ID under the terms of this policy and in accordance with the Terms of Use.

Some Advertisers and/or third-party Advertisement providers (such as agencies or partner ad networks) may use cookies on your computer. The use made by the Advertisers or Advertisement provider of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not to this Policy. If you wish to study the privacy policies of those advertisers you should visit their websites, or contact them directly.

**Google's use of cookies is subject to its own privacy practices and not to this policy**. If you wish to review the Google AdSense privacy policy, then you should visit their website at [www.google.com/adsense](http://www.google.com/adsense) or contact them directly. 

## 10\. _AdSide_ Advertisements

Some Advertisers and/or third-party Advertisement providers (such as agencies or partner ad networks) may use cookies on your computer. The use made by the Advertisers or Advertisement provider of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not to this Policy. If you wish to study the privacy policies of those advertisers you should visit their websites, or contact them directly.

## 11\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

DOCLIX may change and update the terms of this policy from time to time. All substantial changes made to this policy will be notified on adside.com, or in your personal account, at DOCLIX's discretion, and take effect 30 days following their initial posting. Other changes will take effect 7 days following the notification. However, any amendment made to comply with any legal requirements will take effect as legally required.

Continuing to use _ContextGain_ after the changes to this policy have taken effect indicates your acceptance of the amended policy. If you do not agree with any of the amended policy, then you must cease any further use of _ContextGain_.

## 12\. Contact us

You may send requests, responses, questions and complaints, by sending an e-mail message to: [privacy@adside.com](mailto:privacy@adside.com).
